A Guide to the 1930-1999
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Major Volunteer Organizations 1942-1995
  - Richmond Better Housing Coalition (RBHC) 1984-1994
    - Freedom House n.d. 1988-1992 (Box 20)
    - Fund Raising n.d. 1989-1991 (Box 20)
    - Fund Raising Appeal Replies n.d. 1989-1990 (Box 21)
    - Fund Raising Ideas (Box 21)
    - Fund Raising Lunches 1990 (Box 21)
    - Ginter Park Presbyterian Church Building Community in Richmond (Box 21)
    - Governor's Conference on Housing 1988 (Box 21)
    - Governor's Conference on Housing 1990 (Box 21)
    - Governor's Conference on Housing 1992 (Box 21)
    - Grant Proposals (Box 21)
    - Housing Development by Neighborhood Based Organizations Workshop April 15, 1989 (Box 21)
    - Housing the Homeless Committee (Box 22)
    - Housing Tour April 9, 1988 (Box 22)
    - Leadership Metro Richmond-Homelessness and Fair Housing Conference Feb. 7, 1990 (Box 22)
    - Leadership Metro Richmond--Housing Program Jan. 19, 1990 (Box 22)
    - Local Initiatives Support Corporation (LISC)--Announcement Oct. 2, 1990 (Box 22)
    - LISC--Establishing a program in Richmond 1989 (Box 22)
    - LISC--Program Action Review Committee n.d. 1990-1992 (Box 22)
    - LISC--National n.d. 1987-1989 (Box 22)
    - LISC--Richmond 1988-1989 (Box 22)
    - LISC--Richmond 1990 (Box 22)
    - LISC--Richmond 1991 (Box 23)
    - LISC--Richmond 1992 (Box 23)
    - LISC--Richmond 1993 (Box 23)
    - LISC--Richmond 1994 (Box 23)
    - LISC--Richmond--Luncheon Nov. 18, 1988 (Box 23)
    - LISC--Team Visit January 1989 (Box 23)
    - Long Range Planning Committee n.d. 1989-1991 (Box 24)
    - Magazine Articles (Box 24)
    - Meeting Feb. 3, 1988 (Box 24)
    - Meeting Feb. 11, 1988 (Box 24)
    - Meeting Feb. 18, 1988 (Box 24)
    - Membership Meeting April 19, 1988 (Box 24)
    - Membership Meetings 1988-1990 (Box 24)
    - Minutes, Agendas, Notes 1987-1989 (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 24)
    - National Affordable Housing Act 1990 (Box 24)
    - National March for Housing Oct. 7, 1989 (Box 24)
    - Notes from conservations n.d. 1987-1988 (Box 24)
    - Notes-Miscellaneous (Box 24)
    - Pagnoni, Larry n.d. 1989 (Box 24)
    - Planning Committee (Box 24)
    - Plans and Suggestions 1988 (Box 24)
    - Presbyterian Leadership Faire 1988 (Box 24)
    - Prospects 1988-1990 (Box 24)
    - Public Welfare Foundation Proposal Aug. 1989 (Box 24)
    - Retreat January 1988 (Box 24)
    - Retreat Transcript January 1988 (Box 25)
    - Retreats n.d. 1988-1992 (Box 25)
    - Salvation Army 1988 (Box 25)
    - Single Family Production Program 1989 (Box 25)
    - Speech at William Byrd Community House 1989 (Box 25)
    - Speeches: Background Information (Box 25)
    - Speeches: Rough Drafts (Box 25)
    - Strategic Planning Committee Meetings 1988-1989 (Box 25)
    - Street Center Proposal 1988 (Box 25)
    - Street Center 1985 (Box 25)
    - Stuart Circle Parish Council n.d. 1988 (Box 25)
    - Taylor, B.B. (Box 25)
    - Thomas, G. William, Jr. (Manager of Richmond's HUD office) 1987-1988 (Box 25)
    - Turpin, Roland L.--Correspondence, Reports 1984, 1987-1991 (Box 25)
    - Turpin, Roland L.--RRHA controversy, news clippings 1989 (Box 25)
    - United Way Development Fund, Proposal and Budget 1988-1989 (Box 25)
    - VCU and Neighborhood Housing 1988-1989 (Box 25)
    - VHDA (includes report on poverty in Tennessee) 1987 (Box 26)
    - Virginia Center for Housing Research, VPI 1992 (Box 26)
    - Virginia Coalition for the Homeless Shelter Provider Survey1991 (Box 26)
    - Virginia Council on Teen Pregnancy Prevention Report 1991 (Box 26)
    - Virginia Dept. for Children, Report on Homeless in Virginia (Box 26)
    - White House Foundation (Box 26)
    - Yates, Larry--Virginia Low Income Housing Primer 1988 (Box 26)
  - Richmond-on-the-James 1978-1988
    - Richmond-on-the-James 1981-1982 (Box 26)
    - Richmond-on-the-James 1982 (Box 26)
    - Richmond-on-the-James 1983 (Box 26)
    - Richmond-on-the-James 1984 (Box 27)
    - Richmond-on-the-James 1985 (Box 27)
    - Richmond-on-the-James 1985 (Box 27)
    - Richmond-on-the-James 1986 (Box 27)
    - Board Members, Advisory Committee, Statement of Purpose, SCC Authorization 1980-1981 (Box 27)
    - Board of Directors 1987-1988 (Box 28)
    - Community Relations Committee 1985-1987 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence 1980-1982 (Box 28)
    - Financial 1980-1981 (Box 28)
    - Minutes, By-laws 1979-1982 (Box 28)
    - Public Relations 1980 (Box 28)
    - Richmond Chamber of Commerce 1980 (Box 28)
    - Richmond Showcase 1981 (Box 28)
    - Tourism in Richmond 1978-1981 (Box 28)
    - Transportation 1986 (Box 28)
    - Urban Enhancement and Design Committee 1983-1985 (Box 28)
  - Richmond Renaissance 1982-1994
    - Richmond Renaissance (1 of 2) 1982 (Box 29)
    - Richmond Renaissance (2 of 2) 1982 (Box 29)
    - Richmond Renaissance 1983 (Box 29)
    - Richmond Renaissance 1984 (Box 29)
    - Richmond Renaissance 1985 (Box 29)
    - Richmond Renaissance 1986 (Box 30)
    - Richmond Renaissance 1987 (Box 30)
    - Board of Director's Meeting (1 of 2) 7-6-87 (Box 30)
    - Board of Director's Meeting (2 of 2) 7-6-87 (Box 30)
    - Board of Director's Meeting 12-13-88 (Box 30)
    - Board of Director's Meetings n.d. 1988-1989 (Box 30)
    - City Council Partnership Caucus (Box 30)
    - Committe of Sixteen 1983-1985 (Box 31)
    - Council of Organization 1982 (Box 31)
    - Council of Organizations 1983 (Box 31)
    - Council of Organizations 1984 (Box 32)
    - Cultural Link Trolley 1987 (Box 32)
    - Developer List 1983 (Box 32)
    - Evans, Randall J. 1987 (Box 32)
    - Executive Committee, Articles of Incorporation 1982 (Box 32)
    - Executive Committee 1982 (Box 32)
    - Executive Committee January-June 1983 (Box 32)
    - Executive Committee July-December 1983 (Box 33)
    - Executive Committee 1984 (Box 33)
    - Executive Committee 1985 (Box 33)
    - Executive Committee January-May 1986 (Box 34)
    - Executive Committee June-September 1986 (Box 34)
    - Executive Committee October-December 1986 (Box 34)
    - Executive Committee 1987 (Box 34)
    - Executive Committee 1988 (Box 35)
    - Executive Committee 1989 (Box 35)
    - Executive Committee 1990 (Box 35)
    - Executive Committee 1991 (Box 35)
    - Executive Committee 1992 (Box 36)
    - Executive Committee 1993-1994 (Box 36)
    - Executive Committee-Enterprise Development Co./6th Street Market (Box 36)
    - Executive Committee-Gateway Project Plan 1985 (Box 36)
    - Financial 1992-1993 (Box 36)
    - Jackson Ward Project n.d. (Box 36)
    - Marymount School (Speech by MTC) 1983 (Box 36)
    - Newspaper Clippings 1982 (Box 36)
    - Newspaper Clippings 1985 (Box 36)
    - Newspaper Clippings 1987 (Box 36)
    - Newspaper Clippings 1988 (Box 36)
    - Nominating Committee 1993 (Box 36)
    - Planning and Priorities Committee 1984 (Box 36)
    - Riverview Landing 1990 (Box 37)
    - Search Committee 1987 (Box 37)
    - Sixth Street Marketplace Assessment 1989 (Box 37)
    - To be Filed 1989-1990 (Box 37)
    - Urban Symposium Richmond: The Third Century1983 (Box 37)
    - Why the Bridge 1986 (Box 37)
    - Application for Certification as an SBA Section 508 Certified Doucument, oversize (Box 90)
    - Downtown Plan: First Draft 1984, oversize (Box 90)
  - Richmond Urban Forum 1982-1990
    - Richmond Urban Forum 1981-1982 (Box 37)
    - Richmond Urban Forum 1982-1983 (Box 37)
    - Richmond Urban Forum 1983 (Box 38)
    - Richmond Urban Forum 1984-1985 (Box 38)
    - Richmond Urban Forum 1985-1987 (Box 38)
    - Richmond Urban Forum 1987-1988 (Box 38)
    - Richmond Urban Forum 1988-1989 (Box 38)
    - Richmond Urban Forum 1989-1990 (Box 38)
    - Bradley, Ed 1987 (Box 38)
    - Expenses 1981-1982 (Box 38)
    - Expenses 1983-1984 (Box 38)
    - Expenses 1984-1985 (Box 38)
    - Expenses 1985-1986 (Box 38)
    - Expenses 1986-1987 (Box 38)
    - Expenses 1987-1988 (Box 38)
    - Expenses 1988-1989 (Box 38)
    - Expenses 1989-1990 (Box 38)
    - Meeting 10/25/83 (Box 38)
    - Meeting 12/06/83 (Box 38)
    - Meeting 3/6/84 (Box 38)
    - Meeting 10/23/84 (Box 38)
    - Meeting 12/4/84 (Box 39)
    - Meeting 3/19/85 (Box 39)
    - Meeting 10/8/85 (Box 39)
    - Meeting 12/10/85 (Box 39)
    - Meeting 3/11/86 (Box 39)
    - Meeting 10/7/86 (Box 39)
    - Meeting 12/9/86 (Box 39)
    - Meeting 3/10/87 (Box 39)
    - Meeting (Includes MTC's Speech) 10/06/87 (Box 39)
    - Meeting 12/8/87 (Box 39)
    - Meeting 3/8/88 (Box 39)
    - Meeting 10/4/88 (Box 39)
    - Meeting 12/6/88 (Box 39)
    - Meeting 3/7/89 (Box 39)
    - Meeting 10/10/89 (Box 39)
    - Meeting 12/12/89 (Box 39)
    - Meeting 4/13/90 (Box 39)
    - Membership 1986 (Box 39)
    - Membership 1987 (Box 39)
    - Membership 1988-1989 (Box 39)
    - Membership 1989-1990 (Box 39)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts 1957-1993
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts 1960-1961 (Box 39)
    - Anniversary (50th) 1984-1985 (Box 39)
    - Annual Giving Fund Appeal 1987 (Box 40)
    - Board of Trustees Correspondence 1988-1989 (Box 40)
    - Chatsworth Exhibition 1979 (Box 40)
    - Collectors Circle 1968, 1982 (Box 40)
    - Colloquim 1977 (Box 40)
    - Council 1986 (Box 40)
    - Fellows Dinner 1962-1970 (Box 40)
    - Near (Pinkney L.) Tribute 1990 (Box 40)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 40)
    - Party 1989 (Box 40)
    - Plaque 1989 (Box 40)
    - Shakespeare n.d. (Box 41)
    - Theatre Virginia 1984-1985 (Box 41)
    - Theatre Virginia 1985-1987 (Box 41)
    - Theatre Virginia 1986 (Box 41)
    - Theatre Virginia Trustee's Committee 1986-1988 (Box 41)
    - Tyler (John) Portrait 1957 (Box 42)
  - Virginia Statue for Religious Freedom 1983-1995
    - 200 Years of Mr. Jefferson's Idea n.d. (Box 42)
    - Clippings 1985-1987 (Box 42)
    - Constitution, Member List n.d. (Box 42)
    - Correspondence n.d. 1984-1988 (Box 42)
    - Correspondence 1989 (Box 42)
    - Council for America's First Freedom 1986, 1989 (Box 43)
    - Council for America's First Freedom 1989 (Box 43)
    - Council for America's First Freedom 1990 (Box 43)
    - Council for America's First Freedom (1 of 2) 1991 (Box 43)
    - Council for America's First Freedom (2 of 2) 1991 (Box 43)
    - Council for America's First Freedom 1992 (Box 44)
    - Council for America's First Freedom 1993-1994 (Box 44)
    - Board of Director's Meetings 1992-1993 (Box 44)
    - Brochure n.d. (Box 44)
    - Executive Committee 1992-1993 (Box 44)
    - Executive Committee 1993-1994 (Box 45)
    - Film Committee 1985-1987 (Box 45)
    - Film Committee 1987-1988 (Box 45)
    - Film Committee--NEH Application 1986 (Box 45)
    - Film Committee--Proposal 1985 (Box 45)
    - Interim Report 1985 (Box 45)
    - Finance Committee 1992-1993 (Box 46)
    - First Liberty Summit 1988 (Box 46)
    - Minutes 1984-1988 (Box 46)
    - Miscellaneous 1985-1986 (Box 46)
    - Mission Statement (Box 46)
    - Monument Park 1987-1988 (Box 46)
    - Monument Park 1992 (Box 46)
    - Monument Park--Land Sale 1988 (Box 46)
    - Monumental Church n.d. (Box 46)
    - National Conference on Religious Freedom 1986 (Box 47)
    - NEH Proposal n.d. (Box 47)
    - Observance of Religious Freedom Day 1-15-95 (Box 47)
    - Operations Committee 1993 (Box 47)
    - Party Costs 26 Sept. 1991 (Box 47)
    - Photographic reproduction of Virginia Statue for Religious Freedom plaque at State Capitol, oversize (Box 47)
    - Publication for Proposed Center 1992 (Box 47)
    - Quarterly Report 1985-1986 (Box 47)
    - Religious Freedom Article 1993 (Box 47)
    - Religious Freedom Day 1993 (Box 47)
    - Resolution for Religious Freedom 1993 (Box 47)
    - Virginia Court Day 1983-1985 (Box 48)
    - Virginia Foundation for the Humanties n.d. 1986 (Box 48)
    - Virginia Independent n.d. (Box 48)
    - Williamsburg Charter Project 1988 (Box 48)
  - Virginia Historical Society 1990-1994
    - Virginia Historical Society 1990-1991 (Box 48)
    - Board of Trustees 1991 (Box 48)
    - Board of Trustees 1991-1992 (Box 48)
    - Board of Trustees 1993 (Box 49)
    - Board of Trustees--Reports, Programs 1993 (Box 49)
    - Board of Trustees 1994 (Box 49)
    - Collections and Conservation Committee 1992-1994 (Box 49)
    - Fifth Century Fund 1991 (Box 49)
    - Fifth Century Fund 1991-1992 (Box 49)
    - Fifth Century Fund 1992 (Box 50)
    - Fifth Century Fund 1994 (Box 50)
    - Opening Committee 1992 (Box 50)
    - Publications, Articles n.d. 1992 (Box 50)
  - Poplar Forest 1988-1993
    - Poplar Forest 1988 (Box 50)
    - Poplar Forest 1988-1991 (Box 50)
    - Poplar Forest 1992-1993 (Box 51)
    - Brochure n.d. (Box 51)
    - Correspondence 1985 (Box 51)
    - Correspondence 1986-1987 (Box 51)
    - Major Gifts 1990-1991 (Box 51)
    - Report on Phase II 1991 (Box 51)
- Other Organizations 1951-1993
  - American Horticultural Society 1979 (Box 52)
  - Black History Museum and Cultural Center 1986-1991 (Box 52)
  - Central Richmond Association 1985, 1988 (Box 52)
  - Christian Children's Fund 1990-1993 (Box 52)
  - Citizen's Legislative Committee 1981-1984 (Box 52)
  - Civitan Club 1992 (Box 52)
  - Colonial Dames of America 1979-1989 (Box 52)
  - Commission on Human Relations 1982-1986 (Box 53)
  - Cultural Link 1988 (Box 53)
  - Downtown Advisory Committee 1983 (Box 53)
  - Downtown Advisory Committee--Joint Planning Commission 1984-1985 (Box 53)
  - Downtown Advisory Committee--Report, Studies n.d. (Box 53)
  - Garden Club--America 1989 (Box 53)
  - Garden Club--America--Flower Arranging 1990 (Box 53)
  - Garden Club--James River 1962-1988 (Box 53)
  - Garden Club--James River 1964-1965, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Garden Club--James River--Conservation Series 1965 (Box 54)
  - Gettysburg--Virginia Monument 1985-1986 (Box 54)
  - Gettysburg--Virginia Monument 1987 (Box 54)
  - Gillette Forum 1992-1993 (Box 54)
  - George Washington Wine Society 1987-1988 (Box 54)
  - Governor's Arts and Awards Committee 1984-1985 (Box 54)
  - Governor's Commission on Excellence 1990, 1993 (Box 54)
  - Habitat for Humanity 1989-1990 (Box 55)
  - Historic Richmon Foundation 1981-1984 (Box 55)
  - Historic Richmond Roundation 1984-1986 (Box 55)
  - Historic Richmond Foundation--Coloring Book of Richmond Architecture 1982 (Box 55)
  - Historic Richmond Foundation--Policy Committee 1987 (Box 55)
  - Hroswitha Club 1980-1992 (Box 56)
  - Junior League of Richmond n.d. 1938-1939 (Box 56)
  - Junior League of Richmond 1970-1983 (Box 56)
  - Junior League of Richmond 1985-1992 (Box 56)
  - Junior Standards Council-- Directory of the Richmond, VA Public Schools 1954-1955 (Box 56)
  - Junior Standards Council--Handbook (Mss) n.d. (Box 56)
  - Junior Standards Council--Handbook for Junior High School Students n.d. (Box 56)
  - Junior Standards Council--History and Skit n.d. 1956 (Box 56)
  - Junior Standards Council--Miscellaneous n.d. (Box 56)
  - Junior Standards Council--Miscellaneous 1954-1956 (Box 57)
  - Junior Standards Council--Newspaper Clippings 1954-1956 (Box 57)
  - Junior Standards Council--Publicity 1954-1956 (Box 57)
  - Junior Standards Council--Questions asked at First Meeting 1954 (Box 57)
  - Junior Standards Council--Various Publications 1954 (Box 57)
  - Junior Standards Council--Virginia Congress of Parents and Teachers 1956 (Box 57)
  - Kiwanis Club 1988-1992 (Box 57)
  - Kwainis Club--Program Committee 1989 (Box 57)
  - Kwainis Club--Program Committee 1991-1993 (Box 57)
  - Leadership Metro Richmond 1985-1988 (Box 58)
  - Leadership Metro Richmond 1989-1990 (Box 58)
  - Leadership Metro Richmond--Curriculum Committee 1990 (Box 58)
  - Leadership Metro Richmond--Housing Conference 1990 (Box 58)
  - Leadership Metro Richmond--Public Relations Committee 1989-1990 (Box 58)
  - Leadership Metro Richmond--Recruitment 1990-1991 (Box 58)
  - Leadership Metro Richmond--Wintergreen Weekend 1987 (Box 58)
  - Lord Chamberlain Society--Virginia Shakespeare Festival 1982 (Box 59)
  - Metro Richmond 2000 1993 (Box 59)
  - Museum of the Confederacy 1986-1990 (Box 59)
  - Museum of the Conferderacy--Advisory Committee 1990-1993 (Box 59)
  - National Cathedral 1985-1990 (Box 59)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews 1985-1987 (Box 59)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews 1988-1991 (Box 60)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews--Interfaith Breakfast 1989 (Box 60)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews--Interfaith Breakfast 1991 (Box 60)
  - National Society of Arts and Letters 1990-1991 (Box 60)
  - National Society of Arts and Letters 1992-1994 (Box 60)
  - National Society to Prevent Blindness n.d. (Box 61)
  - National Society to Prevent Blindness 1988-1991 (Box 61)
  - Old Dominion Barn Dance 1992 (Box 61)
  - Order of St. John 1969-1982 (Box 61)
  - Order of St. John 1983-1985 (Box 61)
  - Order of St. John 1986-1991 (Box Box 61)
  - Pen Women-National League of America 1981 (Box 62)
  - Poe Foundation 1976-1977 (Box 62)
  - Project Vote! 1981-1982 (Box 62)
  - Raleigh Tavern Society 1981-1982 (Box 62)
  - Richmond Academy of Medicine Auxiliary 2/7/91 (Box 62)
  - Richmond AIDS Ministry (RAM) (Box 62)
  - RAM-AIDS 1991 (Box 62)
  - RAM-AIDS 1992-1993 (Box 62)
  - RAM--AIDS: An Event in Three Acts 1992 (Box 62)
  - RAM--Heart Strings-AIDS Musical 1990 (Box 62)
  - Richmond Area Committee for Public Schools 1958-1959 (Box 63)
  - Richmond Hill 1985-1987 (Box 63)
  - Richmond Hill 1988 (Box 63)
  - Richmond First Club 1987-1990 (Box 63)
  - Richmond First Club 1991-1992 (Box 63)
  - Richmond First Club, Visions 2020 1990-1992 (Box 63)
  - Richmond Forward 1990-1993 (Box 63)
  - Richmond International Festival of Music 1989 (Box 63)
  - Richmond Jaycees 1/3/89 (Box 64)
  - Richmond Rotary Club 8/30/88 (Box 64)
  - Richmond Symphony Foundation 1989-1991 (Box 64)
  - Richmond Symphony Foundation 1991-1993 (Box 64)
  - Richmond Tomorrow 1990-1991 (Box 64)
  - Richmond Urban Institute 1982 (Box 64)
  - Richmond Urban Institute 1983-1985 (Box 64)
  - Richmond Urban League 1984 (Box 64)
  - Shepherd's Center of Richmond 1987-1988 (Box 64)
  - Shockoe Slip Foundation 1983 (Box 64)
  - Sons of Conferderate Veterans 1984-1985 (Box 64)
  - Stratford Hall Book Signing (Box 64)
  - Talking Gardens Foundation, New York Trip 1981 (Box 65)
  - Talking Gardens Foundation of Virginia 1980-1985 (Box 65)
  - Task Force for Historic Preservation 1982-1987 (Box 65)
  - Task Force for Historic Preservation, Newspaper Clippings 1982-1985 (Box 65)
  - Theatre IV 1987-1990 (Box 65)
  - United Givers, Budget Committee 1960-1961 (Box 65)
  - United Way at Work Committee n.d. 1986-1987 (Box 65)
  - United Way Campaign 1990 (Box 65)
  - Unimed (1 of 2) 1988-1991 (Box 65)
  - Unimed (2 of 2) 1988-1991 (Box 66)
  - Unimed-Replies, Medical Incinerator Letter 1991 (Box 66)
  - Virginia Association of Museums 1985-1986 (Box 66)
  - Virginia Association of Realtors-Richmond Association of Realtors Distinguished Citizens Award 1990 (Box 66)
  - Virginia Center for the Performing Arts-Gala., Carpenter Center 1983 (Box 66)
  - Virginia Council on Human Relations 1958-1959 (Box 66)
  - Virginia Cultural Laureate Society 1989 (Box 66)
  - Virginia Heroes 1991 (Box 66)
  - Virginia Home, Junior Board Fashion Show 2/18/84 (Box 66)
  - Virginia Home for Boys 1991 (Box 66)
  - Virginia Women's Cultural History Project (Box 66)
  - Westhampton Jr. Woman Club 1959, 1962 (Box 66)
  - Westminster Canterbury Foundation 1989 (Box 66)
  - Westmoreland Place Association 1980-1987 (Box 66)
  - Woman's Club Tea 1951, 1991 (Box 66)
- Speeches and Articles 1955-1993
  - American Association of Museum Directors 1989 (Box 67)
  - Atlanta Historical Society 1982 (Box 67)
  - Celebration of Volunteerism--Shepherd's Center 1984 (Box 67)
  - Challenge to Our City--Kiwanis Club 1990 (Box 67)
  - Colonial Dames 1985 (Box 67)
  - Douglas Southall Freeman, My Father (Box 67)
  - Douglas Southall Freeman: My Father as a Writer n.d. (Box 67)
  - Efforts for Humanity 1990 (Box 67)
  - For the Love of General Lee--Sons of Confederate Veterans 1985 (Box 67)
  - Freeman File--Virginia Commonwealth University 1988-1989 (Box 67)
  - Ginter Park Presbyterian Church 1991 (Box 67)
  - Ginter Park Presbyterian Church 1993 (Box 67)
  - Ginter Park Woman's Club 1991 (Box 67)
  - Grace and Holy Trinity Church 1988 (Box 67)
  - High Calling--Civil War Round Table 1985 (Box 67)
  - In Praise of Idiosyncrasy--Richmond Public Library 1982 (Box 67)
  - Landscape Design n.d. (Box 67)
  - Lee: The Best Years--Colonial Dames of Washington 1987 (Box 67)
  - Lee: The Best Years--Confederate Museum (Houston) n.d. (Box 67)
  - Mary Davidson Bryan Surgical Wing 1988 (Box 67)
  - Order of St. Luke 1990-1991 (Box 67)
  - Quality of Life 1982 (Box 67)
  - Richmond Memorial Hospital Volunteers 1988 (Box 67)
  - Rotary Club 1988 (Box 67)
  - St. Mary's Episcopal Church 1992 (Box 67)
  - Tuckahoe Woman's Club n.d. 1986 (Box 67)
  - Tuckahoe Woman's Club 1992 (Box 67)
  - Virginia United Methodist Homes, Inc. 1991 (Box 67)
  - Virginia Writer's Club 1986 (Box 67)
  - Virginia Presence 1984-1985 (Box 67)
  - Vision of Community--Greater Richmond Community Foundation (Box 67)
  - Why the Bridge?--Virginia Chapter of the College of Physicians 1986 (Box 67)
  - Woman's Club 1955 (Box 67)
  - Woman's Club 1962 (Box 67)
- Politics 1985-1993
  - Dolan, Bill (Candidate for Attorney General) 1993 (Box 68)
  - Clinton for President 1992 (Box 68)
  - Marsh, Henry Party 7/11/91 (Box 68)
  - Scott, Robert "Bobby" Party 1992 (Box 68)
  - Terry, Mary Sue 1985-1987 (Box 68)
  - Terry, Mary Sue Dinner Party 10/23/85 (Box 68)
  - Terry, Mary Sue Woman's Club 11/17/86 (Box 68)
  - Terry, Mary Sue Newspaper and Magazine Clippings 1985 (Box 68)
  - Terry, Mary Sue 1993 (Box 68)
  - Wilder, Doug Wilder Inauguration 1990 (Box 68)
- Schools, Colleges and Universities 1948-1993
  - Beaumont School for Boys 1959-1963 (Box 69)
  - Collegiate Schools 1990-1991 (Box 69)
  - Governor's School 1992 (Box 69)
  - Hollins College 1979-1984 (Box 69)
  - Hollins College 1987-1993 (Box 69)
  - Hollins College Brewster, Carrol M. (president of college) 1975-1981 (Box 70)
  - Hollins College Article on Carrol M. Brewster by MTC 1981 (Box 70)
  - Hollins College Buildings and Grounds Committee 1980-1985 (Box 70)
  - Hollins College Citation Mary W. K. Ashworth (Box 70)
  - Hollins College Honorary Degree 5/16/93 (Box 70)
  - Hollins College Inauguration 4/10/92 (Box 70)
  - Hollins College Party 11/10/81 (Box 70)
  - Hollins College Portrait of Carrol Brewster correspondence 1980-1982 (Box 70)
  - Hollins College Portrait of Carrol Brewster Photo of portrait (Box 70)
  - Hollins College Presidential Search Commitee 1980-1981 (Box 70)
  - Hollins College Trustees Meeting, Fall 1988 (Box 70)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College 1989 (Box 71)
  - New York University Bellevue Rehabilitation 1948 (Box 71)
  - Potomac School (Mrs. Virginia D. Howard, Director of Development) 1980-1984 (Box 71)
  - Pomfret School 1986-1989 (Box 71)
  - Residential School for Girted Students (Box 71)
  - St. Catherine's School 1961 (Box 71)
  - St. Catherine's School Baccalaureate and Speech by MTC 6/5/82 (Box 71)
  - St. Catherine's School Black Citizens-Opportunities 1962-1964 (Box 71)
  - St. Catherine's School Career Day 5/4/90 (Box 71)
  - St. Catherine's School Centennial Steering Committee 1984-1989 (Box 71)
  - St. Catherine's School Committee for Annual Giving 1961-1963 (Box 71)
  - St. Catherine's School Daisy Days 5/15/83 (Box 71)
  - St. Catherine's School Gala 1990 (Box 71)
  - St. Catherine's School Reunion 1978 (Box 71)
  - St. Catherine's School 50th Reunion 1983 (Box 71)
  - St. Catherine's School Teachers 1961 (Box 71)
  - St. Catherine's School Ella R. Watkins newspaper clipping n.d. (Box 71)
  - St. Paul's College--Bishop Gibson Scholarship Fund 1984 (Box 71)
  - Shady Hill School, Cambridge, MA (Box 71)
  - The Steward School, Richmond, Virginia 1985 (Box 71)